{
"headmasterquestions": [
  {
    "question": "HeadMaster Question Answer A",
    "answerA": "A) A",
    "answerB": "B) B",
    "answerC": "C) C",
    "answerD": "D) D",
    "answerE": "E) E",
    "correctAnswer": "A) A"
  },
  {
    "question": "HeadMaster Question Answer B",
    "answerA": "A) A",
    "answerB": "B) B",
    "answerC": "C) C",
    "answerD": "D) D",
    "answerE": "E) E",
    "correctAnswer": "B) B"
  },  {
    "question": "HeadMaster Question Answer C",
    "answerA": "A) A",
    "answerB": "B) B",
    "answerC": "C) C",
    "answerD": "D) D",
    "answerE": "E) E",
    "correctAnswer": "C) C"
  },  {
    "question": "HeadMaster Question Answer D",
    "answerA": "A) A",
    "answerB": "B) B",
    "answerC": "C) C",
    "answerD": "D) D",
    "answerE": "E) E",
    "correctAnswer": "D) D"
  },  {
    "question": "HeadMaster Question Answer E",
    "answerA": "A) A",
    "answerB": "B) B",
    "answerC": "C) C",
    "answerD": "D) D",
    "answerE": "E) E",
    "correctAnswer": "E) E"
  },  {
    "question": "HeadMaster Question Answer F",
    "answerA": "A) A",
    "answerB": "B) B",
    "answerC": "C) C",
    "answerD": "D) D",
    "answerE": "E) E",
    "correctAnswer": "D) D"
  },  {
    "question": "HeadMaster Question Answer G",
    "answerA": "A) A",
    "answerB": "B) B",
    "answerC": "C) C",
    "answerD": "D) D",
    "answerE": "E) E",
    "correctAnswer": "E) E"
  }, {
    "question": "HeadMaster Question Answer H",
    "answerA": "A) A",
    "answerB": "B) B",
    "answerC": "C) C",
    "answerD": "D) D",
    "answerE": "E) E",
    "correctAnswer": "A) A"
  },
  {
    "question": "HeadMaster Question Answer J",
    "answerA": "A) A",
    "answerB": "B) B",
    "answerC": "C) C",
    "answerD": "D) D",
    "answerE": "E) E",
    "correctAnswer": "B) B"
  },
  {
    "question": "HeadMaster Question Answer K",
    "answerA": "A) A",
    "answerB": "B) B",
    "answerC": "C) C",
    "answerD": "D) D",
    "answerE": "E) E",
    "correctAnswer": "C) C"
  }
]
}